<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on ANECDATA</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on ANECDATA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Azalea Kamellia</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:31:25 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🗺️ &#39;Nature in the HoB (2020) | WWF-Malaysia&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:31:25 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_04/</guid>
      <description>Nature in the Heart of Borneo (2020) A series of maps were created for the book published by WWF-Malaysia and FORMADAT ([Forum Masyarakat Adat Dataran Tinggi Borneo].&#xA;This book was meant as a guide to some of the natural attractions at Northern parts of Sarawak which includes the black gold region of the Sarawak state; Miri, and the pearl of the Borneo island, Sabah. Notable locations of nature&amp;rsquo;s peculiar feats are shared for those who seek to explore the northern states for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🗺️ &#39;The Value of Nature; HoB | WWF-Malaysia&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:37:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_03/</guid>
      <description>I rarely keep record of the maps I make and my portfolio is as thick as an amoeba. But when I find them, I&amp;rsquo;m extra extra happy.&#xA;There are 3 of them in this beautiful coffee table book entitled: &amp;lsquo;The Value of Nature; Balancing Conservation, Development and People in the Heart of Borneo&amp;rsquo;, by my super cool colleague Cynthia Chin &amp;ndash; published by WWF-Malaysia. The digital copy is available in Bahasa Melayu and English at the link below 👇🏻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🗺️ &#39;MBR 2023 | PETRONAS&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_01/</guid>
      <description>Malaysia Bid Round 2023 (MBR 2023) MBR 2023 is a peak event that culminates all the effort of data collection and stock take of hydrocarbon resource in the Malaysia. It is an annual event that put together all the exploration blocks, discoverable hydrocarbon fields and late life assets for upstream sectors to evaluate and invest in.&#xA;Leading up to the event, the Malaysia Petroleum Management (MPM) updates, re-evaluate and produces maps; static and digital, to cater to the need for the most recent stock-take of information that can be obtained from various source of exploration output; seismic, full tensor gradiometry, assets; cables, pipelines, platforms, as well as discoverable resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🟡 &#39;Peta Guna Tanah Malaysia 2014-2018 | FRIM&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/portfolio_02/</guid>
      <description>Peta Gunatanah Malaysia 2014 - 2018 Peta Gunatanah Malaysia 2014 -2018 Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Land Cover 2014 - 2018 web application is a platform generated for the Quality Assessment activity organized by Forest Research Institute Malaysia (FRIM) on 23rd June 2024.&#xA;The workshop aims to collect field/reference data from Malaysian&amp;rsquo;s state agencies in the effort to verify the quality of the land cover classification output generated to support CO2 release measurement from converted agricultural lands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
